Swimming, you lie on a comfortable surface.
You take the arms right out ahead of you and stretch.
It's like somebody's got you right by the hands, you want to stretch those fingers right out.
What you do is you press the pelvis right in to the floor firmly, and lift up your left arm and your right leg.
Some people's down lower, other people, you can lift up higher.
You're connecting opposite energies in the body from the left to the right.
Take a deep breath in, and then exhale.
Switch the right arm and left leg, go higher.
And then inhale, switch.
Again, you can be right down here, exhale, inhale, exhale, some people just barely touch the floor with it.
You work yourself into the levels as you inhale, and exhale, pressing the pelvis right into the floor, and reaching like somebody's got you by the fingers, and somebody else got you by the toes.
Inhale, and exhale.
Keep your shoulders relaxed, and just reach.
And control each movement with the breath as you move, stretching the toes and fingers.
And then just release, come down in the resting posture.
And then guide the floor away from you as you come back up.